KAROL , STĘPIEŃ

+48 603 662 155 karol.stepien@me.com carste.pl github.com/carl-st linkedin.com/in/carl-st

ABOUT

Since the beginning of my career working in the international environment. Each day trying to improve both hard and soft aspects of software development in order to get the most out of the time spent working. Mostly dealing with JS technologies but had quite some experience in native iOS development as well.

Tech nerd, car enthusiast, casual gamer.

Speaking Polish? Check out my podcast -Glosariusz Programisty

Speaking English? Check out my YouTube series - Developer Glossary

Links available on carste.pl



Located in Kraków, Poland Born 07/11/1994

Speaking advanced English (C1) Learning German and Spanish^{*}

EXPERIENCE

12.2018 - Currently Senior Full Stack Engineer Ringier Axel Springer Tech

Taking part in development of six Swiss sites. Direct contact with client, relation building.

React SSR, Redux, GraphQL, TypeScript, Node.js, AWŚ

07.2017 - Currently

Kraków, Poland

Freelancer Carste IT Remotely

Websites, webapps and shops development. Polish clients.

Vanilla JS / React / Next.js, Electron, PWA, Wordpress, Shoper

07.2017 - 12.2018

Front-End Developer Future Processing Gliwice, Poland

SmartCity solution development. Direct contact with French client.

React, Redux, REST, JSON-LD

07.2016 - 11.2016

iOS Developer Yattsi Communications Remotely

Travelling app development. Direct contact with Venezuelan client.

Native iOS Swift application

09.2015 - 05.2016

iOS Developer BCG Digital Ventures Remotely

Mobile service-for-hire apps development. Direct cooperation with US client.

Native iOS Objective-C and Java Android applications

07.2015

iOS Developer Internship Gorrion Software House Gliwice, Poland

Invoice management app development.

Native iOS Swift application

EDUCATION

2017 - 2018

M.Eng, Computer Science Silesian University of Technology

Master thesis: "Intelligent monitoring of sleep quality using lot technology in the Microsoft Azure cloud."

Azure ML vs. CreateML + CoreML Apple Watch and iOS Swift apps using trained Random Forest model

2013 - 2017

B.E., Computer Science Silesian University of Technology

Engineering thesis: "Mulitplatform appointment management system."

MongoDB, Express.js, Angular 2, Node.js (MEAN) Web Application iOS Cliént written in Swift

TECH

React (SSR) Redux Next.js TypeScript Node.is GraphQL

Nest.js (basics) Angular (basics)

AWS Vercel Netlify Jenkins CircleCI TravisCI

Swift & Objective-C

ios sdk

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2016, item 922 as amended.